[Music]
case briefs and so much more LS status
got what you're looking for
in 1998 Krell V Prudential Insurance
case Was Heard by the United States
court of appeals for the third circuit
the case involved an appeal by The
appellants Who challenged the approval
of a settlement and attorney's fees
related to prudential's deceptive
practices The District Court had
certified a national class and approved
the settlement as Fair reasonable and
adequate however the court vacated the
90 million dollars awarded an attorney's
fees and remanded the issue for the
district court to recalculate the fee
accounting for the work done by the
multi-state task force as well as
questioning the multiplier moreover the
court requested the district court to
reconsider whether limited Discovery
should be granted to objectors on the
fee application The District Court
exercised jurisdiction over the class
action approved a certifiable class and
deemed the settlement Fair reasonable
and adequate the court had the power to
award reasonable attorneys fees and
instructed the district court to
recalculate the fee the motion to
discuss qualify was denied and the court
upheld the certification of the proposed
class and the approval of the settlement
but remanded the attorney's fees issue
for further consideration
[Music]
leave the stress of class behind